Resting comfortably, Starscream?
睡得舒服吗 红蜘蛛？
Despite the extend of your injuries,
尽管你伤得不轻
my medical staff assures me that you shall make a rapid recovery.
但我的医务兵向我保证 你很快就能康复
Hopefully, every bit as rapid as your wrath is swift.
但愿您也快点消去心头的怒火
To think that but a short time ago,
想想看 不久之前
it was you who were standing here while I was lying there,
还是你站在这里 而我躺在那里
right after your failed attempt to terminate me.
可惜你棋差一着 没能置我于死地！
But know this, dear Starscream:
不过你记好了 亲爱的红蜘蛛：
our position shall never again be reversed.
你再也休想翻身上位
Starscream, have you lost your senses?
红蜘蛛 你失去理智了吗？
You haven't fully recuperated.
你还没完全康复呢！
I feel fine, Knock Out, never better!
我感觉很好 击倒 再好不过了！
You are a brilliant physician. Now get out of my way!
你真是神医啊 现在给我滚开！
Ahhh... Dark Energon may have replenished your strength, master.
啊…黑暗能量让你恢复了力量 主人
But how could you forget, that you never reclaimed your original shard?
但你难道忘了吗？ 你还没有拿回 你原本的那块碎片
Once the blood of Unicron flows through my veins,
宇宙大帝之血流入我的血脉之日
our positions shall be reversed.
就是我翻身上位之时！
I had hoped that my growing expertise on the subject would remain purely academic,
原以为我对这种东西的了解 仅限于学术方面
but though faint, this is clearly a Dark Energon signature,
但这个微弱的信号 显然又是一股黑暗能量
and it's moving fast.
而且移动迅速
Megatron.
是威震天
Where did he find more the bad stuff?
他又从哪儿找到了那东西？
What's he gonna do with it? Recruiting new army of the undead?
他用那能量要干嘛？组建新的丧尸大军吗？
Zombie-cons?
僵尸虎？
We cannot rule out the possibility,
不能排除这种可能性
especially since Megatron seems to be heading to a familiar site.
特别是 威震天似乎要去一个老地方
Ah, the grave site of the mighty Skyquake.
啊 强大的天震葬身于此
So quick to reject my authority while you lived,
生前你不假思索地拒绝我的领导
but as the first of my reanimated warriors,
但作为被我复活的第一名战士
you shall bow to my command!
你应该听我号令！
Yesss... power of Dark Energon... be mine!
是的…黑暗能量之力…是我的了！
Ahhh.... symbiosis... hahahahaha... I can feel it!
啊…融为一体 哈哈哈…我感觉到了！
Megatron has barely emerged from stasis,
威震天刚从休眠中醒来不久
and it seems he's already making up for lost time.
看来他迫不及待要弥补损失的时间
Bulkhead, Bumblebee, Ratchet, prepare to roll out.
隔板 大黄蜂 救护车 准备出发
Me?
我也去？
If we are dealing with Dark Energon,
如果要对付的是黑暗能量
I may well require your expertise.
我可能需要你的专业知识
Arcee...
阿尔茜…
Bridge operator, got it!
当环陆桥操作员 明白！
Go get'em, Bulkhead. Bring the heart.
干掉他 隔板 把心脏带回来
That's not like Miko not wanna go.
无动于衷 这可不是神子的风格
She's definitely up to something.
她肯定在打什么鬼主意
Make it a break!
快拦住她！
It's not safe.
那不安全！
I'm not gonna miss my first zombie-cons' throwdown!
第一次参加僵尸虎大战 我决不能错过！
Miko?
神子？
That's not Megatron!
那不是威震天！
Rise, Skyquake! Rise!
起来吧 天震！站起来！
Let's see some fight of the living dead already!
快来观赏活死人的战斗吧！
Miko? What were you thinking?
神子 你在想什么？
She wasn't.
她什么都没想
Hey, I totally missed out last time.
嘿 上次我完全错过了
This could be my only chance to take some snaps.
这次也许是惟一的机会 能抓拍几张照片
My cellphone. I must have dropped it back at base.
我的手机 肯定是落在基地了
Starscream.
红蜘蛛！
Autobots?
汽车人？
Stand down.
投降吧！
You stand down.
要投降的是你！
You cannot harm me while Dark Energon flows through my veins!
你伤不了我 黑暗能量已经流遍了我的经脉！
You clipped his wing. He's grounded.
你打断了他的翅膀 他飞不起来了
Come on, come on, rise already!
快啊 快啊 快站起来！
This is Commander Starscream,
我是红蜘蛛指挥官
requesting emergency Ground Bridge to my coordinates.
请向我的坐标紧急开启环陆桥
Ugrrr... I can't believe you make me lose my phone!
真不敢相信 你害我丢了手机！
Eheh, how was this my fault?
怎么成我的错了？
Oh, no.
噢 不
Base to Optimus, the kids are missing.
基地呼叫擎天柱 孩子们不见了
We have a visual, send the GroundBridge immediately.
我们已经看到了 立即打开环陆桥
Two? You three! Into our Ground Bridge, now!
两个？你们三个！进我们的环陆桥 快！
Come on£¡
走吧！
Ratchet, what is happening?
救护车 怎么回事？
The dualing GroundBridge portals must be feeding back on each other.
双重环陆桥的传送门之间 一定是产生了反馈
Miko... we gotta get the kids out of there.
神子…我们得把孩子们救出来
My arm!
我的手！
Not a word about this! To anyone!
不准提起这件事！谁都别说！
Are you guys OK?
你们没事吧？
Yea, I think so.
是的 我想没事
What.. what just happened?
刚…刚才是怎么了？
I can't be certain,
我不敢肯定
but if two GroundBridges sent to the same coordinates crossed streams,
但如果同一坐标的两座环陆桥形成对流
the feedback could have triggered the system overload.
反馈效应可能会引起系统超载
Could? Hello? More like totally did!
可能？嘿 那简直是肯定的！
The kids made it through, right?
孩子们顺利通过了吧？
What's he talking about?
他这话什么意思？
Bulkhead, we are right here!
隔板 我们在这儿呢！
Arcee, did the children make it safely back to base?
阿尔茜 孩子们安全回到基地了吗？
Negative. You don't see them?
没有 你们没看到他们吗？
No sign.
毫无踪影
What? No sign?
什么？毫无踪影？
OK, seriously Bulk?
好吧 别闹了 小隔
Woaaah!
哇！
He went right through you.
他从你身上穿了过去…
We are not alive!
我们不是活人！
I don't wanna be a ghost!
我不想变成鬼魂！
Wait, how can we still touch each other?
等等 为什么我们之间能碰到？
Ratchet, could the children have been
救护车 孩子们有可能被
transported on to the Nemisis instead?
传送到报应号内部吗？
Not likely, if Starscream didn't arrive at our base.
不大可能 既然红蜘蛛没有进入我们的基地
The most likely explanation is a dislocation.
最合理的解释就是定位混乱
The children may simply have been bridged to an unintended destination.
孩子们可能只是被传送到 一个随机的地点
Another place but in the same place?
既不是这里 又正是这里？
Wh... what do you mean?
你…你什么意思？
We're probably in a different dimension.
我们很可能在另一个四维空间
Some kind of alternate reality, a shadowzone.
另一种现实 一个暗影空间
Nerd alert.
书呆子又来了
Look, Skyquake's tomb is empty.
看 天震的墓空了
How do we miss Skyquake rising and shining?
天震死而复生 我们怎么会没发现？
It would seem Starscream got what he came for.
看来红蜘蛛得偿所愿了
Another matter for another time.
以后再考虑这个问题
Right now, our priority is locating Jack, Miko and Raphael.
目前 我们的首要任务是找到杰克 神子和拉斐尔
Arcee, bridge us back to base.
阿尔茜 传送我们回基地
Zombie!
僵尸！
Guys, look out!
伙计们 小心！
Bulkhead!
隔板！
It's right behind you!
它就在你们后面！
Awesome! It can't touch them either.
太好了！连它也碰不到他们
If that thing can't touch the Bots...
如果那东西碰不到汽车人…
Just like we can't...
就跟我们一样
Then we are trapped in a shadowzone, with a Decepticon zombie!
那么和我们一起被困在暗影空间的 就是个霸天虎僵尸！
If we aren't ghosts now, we will be soon.
就算我们现在没死 变鬼魂也是迟早的事
Come on!
快！
Jack, my glasses!
杰克 我的眼镜！
Way too dangerous.
太危险了
I can't see without them.
没有眼镜 我什么都看不见
What are you, ninety£¿
你怎么 七老八十了吗？
Not helping!
别说风凉话！
Fine!
好吧！
Wait!
等等！
Here you go, gramps. Let's book.
拿去吧 小老头 快跑
Maybe we could set up a trap, trying to crash it!
也许能设一个陷阱 想办法砸坏它！
With what? Nothing around here is solid except dusts on the ground.
用什么砸？除了地上的尘土 这儿根本没有实物
We can't run forever. But maybe we can hide.
我们不能一直逃下去 但或许能藏起来
Ratchet, if the children were misdirected to an unintended location,
救护车 如果孩子们被误传到了未指定的地点
is there anyway to get a fix on their coordinates.
有没有办法可以锁定他们的位置？
If they were lost, Miko would have called me by now.
如果他们迷路了 神子应该会打电话给我的
Call them? Yes!
打给他们？没错！
That's why Miko hasn't phoned.
难怪神子没有打电话
Let me try Jack.
我试试打给杰克
The best thing about zombies-- they are slow-moving.
僵尸最好的一点就是 他们很慢 像爬一样
Is that your...
- 是你的… - 电话！
Hello, Arcee?
喂 阿尔茜？
Jack, can you hear me?
杰克 听见了吗？
Nothing.
没声音
Hello, Arcee? Uh, nothing.
喂 阿尔茜？唉 没声音
Gee, imagine that,
天哪 谁想得到
the forth dimension has lausy cellphone reception.
四维空间的手机信号这么差
Hey guys, guys, guys, the phone rang.
嘿 伙计们…电话响了
We are getting a signal.
说明有信号
Maybe the Autobots can't see or hear us because...
汽车人看不见也听不见我们 可能是因为…
we are moving at hyper speed or something.
我们也许在做超高速运动
Do you think that they could read us?
你觉得他们能收到我们的信息吗？
Texting!
短信！
Text me! If my phone is back at base, maybe they'll see it!
给我发短信！如果我的手机在基地 他们或许能看到！
Uh... can you type and run?
呃…你能边跑边发吗？
We are dealling with fluctuating energy profiles inside a wide distortion field,
我们要在一大片扭曲力场中识别波动能量
but it may be possible to back-trace their coordinates.
不过 也许可以反向追踪到他们的坐标
D¨¦j¨¤ vu
似曾相识
What?
什么？
This doesn't look familiar to you?
你不觉得这里看起来很眼熟吗？
Not really.
不觉得
Dude, we just ran one big circle!
老兄 我们只是在绕圈子！
Sweet!
太棒了！
It must have gone trapped in here during the explosion, too.
它一定也是在爆炸时被困在这儿的
Well, if it's solid, we can use it.
既然这是个真家伙 我们就能用
Uh, Starscream, I don't quite understand how this could have happened.
呃 红蜘蛛 我想不通 这是怎么搞的
And yet, it did!
不通也得通！
Can you imagine my horror?
你能想象我有多惊慌吗？
There I am, minding my own business, when my arm just falls off!
当时我在想事情 我的手臂突然自己掉了！
Clearly Megatron inflicted more damage upon me than you realize!
显然 威震天对我造成的伤害 不是你想的那么简单！
Doctor...
医生…
Well, on the bright side,
这样吧 想开点
this provides an excellent opportunity for an upgrade.
这正是个升级的绝好机会
Uh.. let's see, you could go with this sonic cannon.
唔…我看看 你可以试试这个声波炮
It's reliable, low maintenance, although it lacks of certain flare.
很稳定 维护简单 只是不大气派
Personally I prefer the null-ray.
我个人推荐氖射线
It has just the right mix of flash and fire power.
闪光和火力的搭配恰到好处
I don't want a new model!
我不想换新设备！
I just want the same arm I had before!
我只想让我的手臂完好如初！
But Starscream, your equipment is a bit... obsolete...
但是红蜘蛛 你的装备有点…过时了
I'm not sure I have another one lying around.
不知道还有没有废旧的备用品
Of course we could try to salvage yours-- you kept it, didn't you?
当然了 也可以尝试用原肢修复――原肢你还留着吧？
It was beyond recovery.
已经…无法修复了
Anyone know how to fire this thing?
谁知道怎么发射这玩意儿？
I don't see a trigger.
我没看到扳机
Starscream did something with his fingers.
红蜘蛛似乎是通过手指来操作的
We have one shot. We need to make it count.
只能发射一次 要一击命中
How do you like us now?
还敢惹我们吗？
Come on, come on!
快 快！
How can a zombie arm move faster than the actual zombie?
为什么僵尸的手 比它本身跑得还快？
Miko's phone.
神子的电话
It wan't blinking before.
刚才它没闪过
It's a message.
是条信息
"In alternate dimension with zombie. Help!"
“与僵尸同被困在另一个空间 救命！”
That doesn't sound possible.
听起来很离谱
Ratchet, can we triangulate the geographical position
救护车 能确定手机信号的地理位置吗？
In a parallel dimensional plane?
在平行四维空间里？
Let's find out.
我们试试看
My Dark Energon shard.
我的黑暗能量碎片
Pulsing? My warrior lives!
有脉冲？我的战士还活着！
Ahh... Look what I found in storage.
啊…看看我在仓库找到了什么
What are you doing?
你又干什么去？！
You were right, Knock Out.
你说的没错 击倒
I'm much too attached to my original appendage.
我跟原来的零件太有感情了
I will retrieve it.
我会找回来的
Now, calculating for relative time delays and iron spheric distortions,
通过计算相对时差和球面畸变数据
the signal eminated from the exact location
信号的发射源地点
as the original GroundBridge coordinates!
和之前的环陆桥坐标完全相同！
But we already looked for them there.
但我们在那儿找过了
Perhaps, but not in the correct dimensional phase as their message stated.
虽然找过 但却找错了空间 如他们的短信所说
But, if I can recreate the feedback loop which triggered the event,
不过 如果我重新启动引发事故的那个反馈循环
I might be able to generate a rescue portal,
应该能生成一个营救传送门
allowing passage from their dimension...
从他们所在的空间…
Back to base?
传送回基地？
No! We are talking about inter-dimensional travel here, Bulkhead!
不！这可是跨空间传送 隔板！
Attempting to redirect the vortex trajectory would be far too risky.
将漩涡轨道重新定向 风险太大！
Everyone knows that.
大家都明白
If the coordinates aren't precisely the same,
如果坐标不是绝对一致
who knows where the humans could wind up?
他们会被传送到哪儿 谁都不知道！
Oh, come on!
噢 拜托！
This place is like one big merry-go-round.
这地方就像个大型旋转木马
Skyquake? You master summons you!
天震？你的主人在召唤你！
How'd that freak get into our dimension?
那个怪胎怎么跑进了我们的空间？
He didn't. He can't see us.
他没进来 他看不见我们
Forget Starscream, we get to run...
别管红蜘蛛了 我们得继续跑！
some more.
再跑一圈…
A GroundBridge portal?
环陆桥传送门？
That has to be a way out of here.
一定是出口！
The Autobots saw our texts.
汽车人看到我们的信息了
What? Mine? Or theirs?
什么？我的？还是他们的？
If we go through, we will smack into Starscream.
如果我们穿过去 一定会跟红蜘蛛碰面
If we don't...
如果我们不过去…
We are zombie chow.
就变成僵尸的盘中餐
Option 3, we get running in circles.
还有第三个选择 继续绕圈跑
Follow my lead.
听我口令
Now!
跑！
Humans? Where did you vermin...
人类？你们这堆虫子从哪儿…
No!
不！
This isn't mine... ah... Unhand me!
这不是我的手…啊…
Jack, Miko, Raphael.
杰克 神子 拉斐尔
Ah, Autobots again?
啊 又是汽车人？
Requesting emergency GroundBridge, now!
请求开启紧急环陆桥 快！
Look, if you are gonna blame anybody, blame me.
听着 如果要责备谁的话 就拿我开刀吧
I'm sorry, could you repeat that a couple of dozen times?
不好意思 你能重说几十遍吗？
Miko, what you endured has been lesson enough.
神子 你的经历算是给你足够的教训了
We are just glad you are all safe.
你们安然无恙 我们就放心了
Guess it was a good thing you dropped this.
幸好你落下了这个
Too bad you didn't get any pictures though.
可惜你一张照片都没拍到
Nah, that's OK.
算了 没什么
I think after today,
我想 从今以后
I pretty much have zombie close-up seared into my brain.
僵尸的特写镜头 已经深深烙在我脑子里了
What happened? Megatron pound you like scrap metal again?
怎么回事？威震天又把你当破铜烂铁砸了一遍？
I would rather not discuss it.
我不想提了
Honestly Starscream, you need to take better care of yourself.
老实说 红蜘蛛 你得善待自己一点
Didn't you retrieve your limb?
你没捡回你的手臂吗？